听力考试正式开始，请看听力部分第一节。
第一节。
也听下面五段对话。
每段对话后有一个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的。相应位置。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间
来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。
你将听到以下内容：“
Excuse me, can you tell me how much the shirt is?
Yes, it's 9.15.
你将有五秒钟的时间，将正确答案
标在试卷上。
衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，所以
你选择。
项，并将其标在试卷上。
现在，你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第一小题的有关内容
What time is your train leaving?
It leaves at ten.
I've got fifty minutes left.
You'd better hurry, or you won't be able to catch it.
Nice weather we're having, don't you think?
No, it is too cold.
I think it is just right.
I'd prefer it a few degrees warmer.
Now let's stop talking and get going.
I need to be in my office in fifteen minutes, or I'll be late for a meeting.
Okay, bye. This course is really difficult.
I don't think it's all that bad, and we'll benefit a lot from it.
So you're taking it too.
That's true. Could you turn that off?
I can't hear myself think.
What? The radio.
Oh, sorry. Hi, Michael.
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后。
有几个小题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听每段对话或独白前，
你将有时间约。
阅读各个小题，每小题
五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍
听下面一段对话。
回答第六和第七两个小题。
现在，你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两个小题。
I heard you just came back from a holiday?
Yes, I stayed for a week in China and five days in India.
You do travel a lot, don't you?
Last year you went to Norway, right?
Well, I've been to quite some countries, but not yet to Norway.
Last summer I toured Russia for two weeks.
Hi, Michael. I heard you just came back from a holiday?
Yes, I stayed for a week in China and five days in India.
You do travel a lot, don't you?
Last year you went to Norway, right?
Well, I've been to quite some countries, but not yet to Norway.
Last summer I toured Russia for two weeks.
听下面一段对话，回答
第八和第九两个小题。
现在你。
有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
Sally, do you like seafood?
Yes, of course.
Is there anything you especially like?
Well, I really don't know.
I can never remember the names.
Okay. Is there any food you don't eat?
Well, I don't eat chicken, and I don't like eggs either, but I like all kinds of
fish and vegetables.
Then let's look at the menu and see what they've got for us.
Sally, do you like seafood?
Yes, of course.
Is there anything you especially like?
Well, I really don't know.
I can never remember the names.
Okay. Is there any food you don't eat?
Well, I don't eat chicken, and I don't like eggs either, but I like all kinds of
fish and vegetables.
Then let's look at the menu and see what they've got for us.
听下面一段对话，回答
第十至第十二三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
You look pale, Stephanie.
What's wrong? I don't feel good.
I have a bad headache.
In fact, I haven't got much sleep this past week and I feel really tired.
Why don't you go to see a doctor?
Yeah, I think I should, but I have a report due tomorrow.
Ms. Jenkins needs it for the board meeting next Monday.
Well, it's Wednesday today.
Why don't you talk to Ms.
Jenkins and ask if you can hand it in on Friday morning?
Maybe I should try.
I guess I just need a good sleep.
Thanks, George. If you need any help with the report, just let me know.
You look pale, Stephanie.
What's wrong? I don't feel good.
I have a bad headache.
In fact, I haven't got much sleep this past week and I feel really tired.
Why don't you go to see a doctor?
Yeah, I think I should, but I have a report due tomorrow.
Ms. Jenkins needs it for the board meeting next Monday.
Well, it's Wednesday today.
Why don't you talk to Ms.
Jenkins and ask if you can hand it in on Friday morning?
Maybe I should try.
I guess I just need a good sleep.
Thanks, George. If you need any help with the report, just let me know.
听下面一段对话。
回。
答第十三至第十六四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Anything interesting in the paper today, dear?
Well, yeah. There are a few here that might interest us.
Here's one for just $400.
It only has one bedroom, but it sounds nice, near Lake Street.
Yeah. Let me see what the cheapest two -bedroom apartment is.
Oh, here's one on Market Street.
It's a real bargain.
Only $350. But it doesn't have any furniture.
Well, it costs a lot to buy all the furniture.
Oh, here's another one for just over $400.
This sounds very interesting.
It's on South Street.
That's a nice area.
Yes, it's quiet.
Did you say two bedrooms?
Yes, at $415.
Why don't we go and have a look?
Okay. I'll give them a call.
Anything interesting in the paper today, dear?
Well, yeah. There are a few here that might interest us.
Here's one for just $400.
It only has one bedroom, but it sounds nice, near Lake Street.
Yeah. Let me see what the cheapest two -bedroom apartment is.
Oh, here's one on Market Street.
It's a real bargain.
Only $350. But it doesn't have any furniture.
Well, it costs a lot to buy all the furniture.
Oh, here's another one for just over $400.
This sounds very interesting.
It's on South Street.
That's a nice area.
Yes, it's quiet.
Did you say two bedrooms?
Yes, at $415.
Why don't we go and have a look?
Okay. I'll give them a call.
听下面一段独白。
回答第十七至第二十四个小题。
现在你有二十秒。
闹钟的时间。
阅读这四个小题。
Look at this picture.
It's the London Tea Trade Centre.
As you can see, it is on the north bank of the River Thames.
It is the centre of an important industry in the everyday lives of the British
people. Tea is the British national drink.
Every man, woman and child over 10 years of age has on average over 4 cups a day, or
some 1,500 cups annually.
About 30 of the world's exports of tea makes its way to London, and Britain is by
far the largest importer of tea in the world.
Now in the second picture, you can see how tea is tasted in the Tea Trade Centre
before it is sold.
Here, different types of tea are tasted by skilled tea tasters before they're sold
at each week's tea sale.
It's amazing to see them at work.
Over a hundred kinds of are laid out in a line on long tables.
The tasters generally taste teas with milk, since that is how the majority of
British people drink their tea.
The tasters move down the line with surprising speed, tasting from a spoon and
deciding what is a fair price for each tea.
After that, they...
Look at this picture.
It's the London Tea Trade Centre.
As you can see, it is on the north bank of the River Thames.
It is the centre of an important industry in the everyday lives of the British
people. Tea is the British national drink.
Every man, woman and child over 10 years of age has on average over 4 cups a day, or
some 1,500 cups annually.
About 30 of the world's exports of tea makes its way to London, and Britain is by
far the largest importer of tea in the world.
Now in the second picture, you can see how tea is tasted in the Tea Trade Centre
before it is sold.
Here, different types of tea are tasted by skilled tea tasters before they're sold
at each week's tea sale.
It's amazing to see them at work.
Over a hundred kinds of are laid out in a line on long tables.
The tasters generally taste teas with milk, since that is how the majority of
British people drink their tea.
The tasters move down the line with surprising speed, tasting from a spoon and
deciding what is a fair price for each tea.
After that, they...
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案
转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you for watching!
you you you
听力部分到此结束。